export const QuizData = [
    {
        question: "Which team has won the most UEFA Champions League titles as of 2022??",
        options:[ " Barcelona", " Real Madrid", " Bayern Munich", " AC Milan"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the all-time top scorer in the history of UEFA Champions League?",
        options:["Lionel Messi", "Cristiano Ronaldo", "Robert Lewandowski", "Raul"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which team has won the most consecutive UEFA Champions League titles?",
        options: ["Barcelona", " AC Milan", " Bayern Munich", " Real Madrid"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Which country has the most UEFA Champions League winners?",
        options: ["Spain", "Italy", "England", "Germany"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the youngest player to score a goal in a Champions League final?",
        options:[ " Raheem Sterling", "Patrick Kluivert", "Lionel Messi", "Gareth Bale"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which manager has won the UEFA Champions League with three different clubs?",
        options:["Jose Mourinho", "Pep Guardiola", "Carlo Ancelotti", "Jurgen Klopp"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which team won the first edition of the UEFA Champions League in the 1955-1956 season?",
        options: ["AC Milan", "PSG", "Real Madrid", "Barcelona"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Who scored the fastest goal in UEFA Champions League history?",
        options: ["Roy Makaay", "Paolo Maldini", "Neymar Jr", " Alessandro Del Piero"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question: "Which club has reached the most UEFA Champions League finals without winning the title?",
        options: [" Atletico Madrid", "Barcelona", "Arsenal", "Juventus"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Which player has won the UEFA Champions League with three different clubs?",
        options: ["Cristiano Ronaldo", " Lionel Messi", "Gerard Pique", "Andres Iniesta"],
        answer: 1
    }
];